== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Raj:)What time do you
and Bernadette head out?
(Howard:)As soon as I get home.
(Howard:)We're hoping to make it
before dark.
(Raj:)I've never been
to Palm Springs.
(Stuart:)Oh, you
should go.
(Stuart:)It's terrific.
I-I really thrive anywhere
(Stuart:)the women and the temperature
are over 90.
(Raj:)I don't know.
(Raj:)If I want to watch
old people sweat,
(Raj:)I can just FaceTime
my family in India.
(Stuart:)It's nice you
(Stuart:)and Bernadette are getting away.
(Howard:)Well, she wants us to
spend more time together
(Howard:)before the baby comes.
(Stuart:)So then what are you doing here
buying comic books?
(Howard:)Well, he wants us to
spend more time together
(Howard:)before the baby comes.
(Leonard:)When you live with someone,
there's gonna be conflict.
(Leonard:)You just have
to keep communicating.
(Sheldon:)I'm open to that.
(Amy:)Okay. Well, for starters,
(Amy:)there's nothing wrong
with keeping our toothbrushes
(Amy:)in the same holder.
(Penny:)Sheldon, what do you say
to that?